I'm Amanda Seals. Of course, I'm always giving you smart, funny, black content.
I'm Amanda Seals. Of course, I'm always taking y'all with me when I'm on the move.
Judge Sutter!
I'm Amanda Seals. Of course, I'm an independent artist,
because I would rather impress the people than impress Hollywood.
I'm Amanda Seals. Of course, I'm going to ask you, have you been to therapy?
I'm Amanda Seals. Of course, on Instagram, people think I'm always angry about something,
but on Patreon, they see I'm living a life.
Yes, I'm Amanda Seals. Of course, I'm here doing this damn video,
because I got young people working for me that said this is the trend right now on the internet.
Y'all, I just came here to tell y'all I have a new tier launching on Patreon.
It's the Baldwin tier, and it has access to small doses podcast videos.
You're going to get clips of me on the road doing this stand-up thing.
You also get access to lives of me doing painting,
of me talking about all different types of topics, of me watching shit, etc.
So, please, come through, support a sister who's doing real things,
and talking about real things, and doing it on her own time, in her own space.
Of course, I was going to not be able to stick with the plan.
Y'all know I'm a rabble!